Guide to the Stephen Sandy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 2003 Acquisition, 1938-2003; 4; 15.83; (17 boxes)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - Northwest Review, 1962 May 9 (Box 10)
    - Nova, Craig, 1990-2002 (Box 10)
    - Nunley, Richard, 1983-1993, undated (Box 10)
    - Nurkse, Dennis, 1986-2002, undated (Box 10)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, 1979 February 13 (Box 10)
    - Olds, Sharon, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Oliver, Mary, 1996-1997, undated (Box 10)
    - Olmer, Paul, undated (Box 10)
    - Orr, Gregory, 1993, undated (Box 10)
    - Paglia, Camille, 1972-1973, undated (Box 10)
    - Painter, Charlotte, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
    - Paley, Grace, 1990 June 23 (Box 10)
    - Paley, Maggie, 2000-2001, undated (Box 10)
    - Palmer, David, 1990 (Box 10)
    - The Paris Review, 1993, undated (Box 10)
    - Parisi, Joseph, 1984-1994 (Box 10)
    - Parker, Will, 1992 June 16 (Box 10)
    - Parks, Stephen, 1994, undated (Box 10)
    - Partisan Review, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Paton, John, 1982 June 16 (Box 10)
    - Payne, David, 1994-2001 (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Peck, John, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
    - Peck, Robert, 1972 April 14 (Box 10)
    - Pennsylvania (University of) Press, 1996-1999 (Box 10)
      Penn Greek Series
    - Perelman, Abby and Peter D. L. Stansky, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Peters, Alton, 1996 April-May (Box 10)
    - Peters, Robert, 1981-1984, undated (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Robert, 1959-1960 (Box 10)
    - Pettingell, Malcolm, 1998 August 7 (Box 10)
    - Pettingell, Phoebe, 1988-2001, undated (Box 10)
    - Pevear, Richard, 1980 June 4 (Box 10)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 10)
    - Ploughshares, 1995 June 5 (Box 10)
    - Plumly, Stanley, 1972-1998 (Box 10)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 10)
    - Poirier, Richard, 1973-1986 (Box 10)
    - Polite, Frank, undated (Box 10)
    - Pollan, Michael, 1992 April 5 (Box 10)
    - Porte, Joel, 1985-1987 (Box 11)
    - Porter, David, 1999-2002, undated (Box 11)
    - Porter, Joe Ashby, 1988-1994 (Box 11)
    - Potter, Nancy, 1966 August 9 (Box 11)
    - Price, Martin, 1970 December 24 (Box 11)
    - Prose, Francine, 1994 August 30 (Box 11)
    - Purl, Linda, 1993 July 13 (Box 11)
    - Quinn, Alice, 1989-1997 (Box 11)
    - Rago, Christina, [no year] September 2 (Box 11)
    - Rago, Henry, 1966 August 1 (Box 11)
    - Rakosi, Carl, 1968-1979 (Box 11)
    - Ramke, Bin, 1998-2002, undated (Box 11)
    - Randall, Julia, 1988-2000, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Random House, Inc., 1967 March 16 (Box 11)
    - Rath, Roger, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Rector, Liam, 1993-1996 (Box 11)
    - Reed, J. D., 1969-1972, undated (Box 11)
    - Reed, Mark, 1964-2001 (Box 11)
    - Reichblum, Bill, 2000-2002 (Box 11)
    - Restrat, Alain-Christophe, undated (Box 11)
    - Richards, I. A., 1965-1972 (Box 11)
    - Rivard, David, 1996-1998 (Box 11)
    - Robbins, Susannah, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Frank, 1995-1999, undated (Box 11)
    - Roethke, T., 1993, undated (Box 11)
    - Romer, Christopher, 1993-2000 (Box 11)
    - Ronk, Martha, 1993-1997 (Box 11)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1966-2002, undated (Box 11)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, 1991, undated (Box 11)
    - Rosenberg, Liz, 1975-1987, undated (Box 11)
    - Rudenstine, Neil, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Rudman, Mark, 1997, undated (Box 11)
    - Ruefle, Mary, 1979-1998, undated (Box 11)
    - Running, Daniel, 1995-1997 (Box 11)
    - Ryberg, Carl W., 1967 (Box 11)
    - Ryberg, Charles, 1964-1971 (Box 11)
    - Ryberg, Dorothea, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - Salter, Mary Jo, 1992-1996 (Box 11)
    - Salzman, Eva, 1990-2001, undated (Box 11)
    - The San Francisco Review, 1962, undated (Box 11)
    - Sanavio, Piero, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Sanders, Tony, 1988-1996 (Box 11)
    - Sandy, Alan, 1956-2000 (Box 11)
    - Sapphire, 2001 August 27 (Box 11)
    - Sayre, Nora, 1985-2001, undated (Box 11)
    - Schevill, James, 1969-1995 (Box 11)
    - Schneebaum, Tobias, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Schulman, Grace, 1981-2000 (Box 11)
    - Schulman, Sam, 1995, undated (Box 11)
    - Seay, James, 1998 February (Box 11)
    - Segal, Erich, 1971 June 30 (Box 11)
    - Segal, Lore, 1991 August 8 (Box 11)
    - The Sewanee Review, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Shackelford, Rudy, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Shandorf, Tom, undated (Box 11)
    - Shapiro, David, 1985 May 6 (Box 11)
    - Shapiro, Jane, 1993-1995 (Box 11)
    - Share, Don, 2000-2001, undated (Box 11)
    - Shawn, Allen, 1992-2001, undated (Box 11)
    - Sheaffer, Lou, 1969, undated (Box 11)
    - Shepherd, Reginald, 1995 February 1 (Box 11)
    - Shinagel, Michael, 1984-1998 (Box 11)
    - Shinder, Jason, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Sifton, Elizabeth, 1997 March 25 (Box 11)
    - Simic, Charles, 1973-1984, undated (Box 11)
    - Slavitt, David, 1954-2002, undated; 3 (Box 11)
    - Sleigh, Tom, undated (Box 12)
    - Smartish Pace, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Smith, Bruce, 1997, undated (Box 12)
    - Smith, Dave, 1981-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Snodgrass, W. D., 1978 December 13 (Box 12)
    - Solomon, Hyde, 1965, undated (Box 12)
    - Souter, David, 1991 September 6 (Box 12)
    - Spacks, Barry, 1965-1969, undated (Box 12)
    - Spiegel, Maura, 1985 May 6 (Box 12)
    - Spiegelman, Willard, 1980-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Spivack, Kathleen, 1970-1997 (Box 12)
    - St. Armand, Barton L., 1982-2001 (Box 12)
    - Stansky, Peter D. L., 1993 April 1 (Box 12)
    - Starbuck, George, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Steele, Max, 1985 February 13 (Box 12)
    - Steiner, George, 1977 December 6 (Box 12)
    - Stern, Gerald, 1984-1988 (Box 12)
    - Stern, Jared, undated (Box 12)
    - Story Line Press - Constance Warloe, 1998-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Strand, Mark, 1995-1997, undated (Box 12)
    - Stryck, Lucien, 1972-1978 (Box 12)
    - Summers, Robert L., 1970 October 9 (Box 12)
    - Swan, John, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Swann, Brian, 1979-1981 (Box 12)
    - Sward, Robert, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Swenson, Karen, 1971-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Swenson, Tree, 1994-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Symes, Carol, 1999-2001 (Box 12)
    - Takano, Masao, 1968-1996; 3 (Box 12)
    - Targan, Barry, 1981 (Box 12)
    - Tate, James, undated (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Benjamin, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1987 September 5 (Box 12)
    - Texier, Catherine, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Thomas, Harry, 1994-1995, undated (Box 12)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, 1984-1994 (Box 12)
    - Tokunaga, Shozo, 1963-1998, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Tonis, Robert, 1966-1998, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Townley, Hugh, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Turco, Lewis, 1993 May 17 (Box 12)
    - United States Department of Education, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Unterecker, John, 1981 January 4 (Box 12)
    - Van Duyn, Mona, undated (Box 12)
    - Vendler, Helen, 1979-1997 (Box 12)
    - Vermont Studio Center, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
    - Viscusi, Mario, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
    - Vivante, Arturo, 1986-2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Voigt, Ellen Bryant, 1975-1992 (Box 12)
    - Wadsworth, William, 1993-2002 (Box 12)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1970-1987, undated (Box 12)
    - Waldrop, Rosmarie, 1973-1979 (Box 12)
    - Wallace, Thomas C., 1961-1967 (Box 12)
    - Ward, Aileen, 1999, undated (Box 12)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1940 (Box 12)
    - Warren, Rosanna, 1998, undated (Box 12)
    - Warsowe, Allan, 1966, undated (Box 12)
    - Washington Square, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Watt, Ian, 1969 February 20 (Box 12)
    - Weil-Sayre, Sylvie, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Weingarten, Roger, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Weiss, Theodore & Renee, 1967-1979, undated (Box 12)
    - Weld, George, 1994-1999 (Box 12)
    - Welter, Rush, 1991-1996 (Box 12)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1981-1998 (Box 12)
    - West, Michael, 1971, undated (Box 12)
    - Wetsteon, Rachel, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Wheatley, James H., undated (Box 12)
    - Wheeler, Susan, 1993 January 28 (Box 12)
    - Wier, Dara, 1984-1988 (Box 12)
    - Wilbur, Richard, 1978-1994 (Box 13)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1938 (Box 13)
    - Wilk, David, 1975-1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Williams, C. K. (Charles Kenneth), 1973 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Galen, 2001 May 22 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Gil, 1975-1977, undated (Box 13)
    - Williams, Robert, 1991-1994 (Box 13)
    - Wilner, Eleanor, 2000 December 13 (Box 13)
    - Wilson, Richard, 1968-1999, undated; 2 (Box 13)
    - Winch, Terry, 1996-1998, undated (Box 13)
    - Winterrowd, Wayne, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Winters, Anne, 1996-1997, undated (Box 13)
    - Wofford, Philip, undated (Box 13)
    - Wolf, Daniel, 1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Woo, David, 1993 April 3 (Box 13)
    - Woodring, Carl, 1968 November 18 (Box 13)
    - Woods, Rosemary, 1969-1981 (Box 13)
    - Wormser, Baron, [no year] August 24 (Box 13)
    - Wright, Charles, 1991-1998 (Box 13)
    - Yaddo, 1968-2002, undated (Box 13)
    - Yale University Press, 1962 June 7 (Box 13)
    - Young, David, 1978 March 3 (Box 13)
    - Young, Kevin, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Young, Vernon, 1977 June 18 (Box 13)
    - Young, W. C. Burriss (incoming and outgoing), 1963-1997, undated; 4 (Box 13)
    - Zara, Louis, 1966 July 27 (Box 13)
    - Zarin, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Zimmer, Paul, 1983-1993 (Box 13)
    - Zimmerman, T. Price, 1989-2001 (Box 13)
    - Zukofsky, Louis and Celia, 1966, undated (Box 13)
    - Army correspondence, 1956-1957, undated (Box 13)
    - Atlanta Read Trip, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Fan letters, 1968-2001 (Box 13)
    - Japan - Professors, 1967-1988, undated (Box 13)
    - Letters for editors, miscellaneous, 1976-2002 (Box 13)
    - Letters from students, 1977-1988 (Box 13)
    - Readings, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - Unsorted letters, 1962-1967, undated; 2 (Box 13)
  - Writings
    Portions are arranged roughly alphabetically.
    - Stresses in the Peaceable Kingdom, 1966; 7 (Box 14)
    - "Academic Lament", undated (Box 14)
    - "After a Party at Jean Carmel's", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Ballad of Mary Baldwin", undated (Box 14)
    - "Butterfly and Snake", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Destruction of Bullfinch's House", undated (Box 14)
    - "Doubling Back", undated (Box 14)
    - "Driving Down to D.C.", undated (Box 14)
    - "Et Quid Amabo Nisi Quod Aenigma Est", undated (Box 14)
    - "Flag Nights", 1966 July-August (Box 14)
    - "The Forrester and Waterfall", undated (Box 14)
    - "Gansevoort to Bacon Hill", undated (Box 14)
    - "Home from the Range", undated (Box 14)
    - "Isaac Jogues", undated (Box 14)
    - "Let Us All Stand and Sing Together", undated (Box 14)
    - "Letter to a Maniac", undated (Box 14)
    - "A Man Is Not Called an Irishman Until He Is Forty", undated (Box 14)
    - "Midsummer Night", undated (Box 14)
    - "Morning Above the Delaware", undated (Box 14)
    - "Moving In", undated (Box 14)
    - "My Window", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Night, the Day", undated (Box 14)
    - "A Note from Machado", 1967 (Box 14)
    - "Now Sometimes", undated (Box 14)
    - "Old Golden", undated (Box 14)
    - "Out on the Tide", undated (Box 14)
    - "A Patriotic Song for Iceland", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Pilgrim Tourist", undated (Box 14)
    - "Poem for a Girl Who Wanted to Know What a Fur Below Was", undated (Box 14)
    - "Programming the Earthly Paradise", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Return", undated (Box 14)
    - "Reutlinger's Place", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Room", undated (Box 14)
    - "Soaking", undated (Box 14)
    - "Snow on the River", undated (Box 14)
    - "A Somber Welter, a Tender Drowsing", undated (Box 14)
    - "Summer Letter", 1967 (Box 14)
    - "Ultra-Sentiment and Infra-Thought", undated (Box 14)
    - "Waking Again in Joy", undated (Box 14)
    - "Walking Around You", undated (Box 14)
    - "What Brings Us Home", undated (Box 14)
    - "The Basic Training of Henry Czysiak", 1967; 3 (Box 14)
    - "The Cycle: a Story", undated (Box 14)
    - The Good-Time War: a Local History, 1967; 36 (Box 14)
    - The Good-Time War: A Local History, 1967; 13 (Box 15)
    - "What Are You Doing That Is So Important?", undated; 5 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous notes and poems, 1960-1961, undated; 3 (Box 15)
    - "Casualties", undated (Box 15)
    - "Charley", 1967 September 7 (Box 15)
    - "For Mr. Reed of Martha's Vineyard", undated; 2 (Box 15)
    - "History Major", undated (Box 15)
    - Japanese Room, 1969 (Box 15)
    - "Sam's Line", undated (Box 15)
    - "Sleep on the Floor", undated (Box 15)
    - "Spring Clear", undated (Box 15)
    - "The Military", undated (Box 15)
    - "The Two Lords of Maeda", undated (Box 15)
    - "To Caelius", undated (Box 15)
    - "Welcome Back", undated (Box 15)
    - "Where I Was", undated (Box 15)
    - "Japan, the Land", undated (Box 15)
    - "Sewn Straw, Exact Pattern...", undated (Box 15)
    - Notes for an unidentified poem, undated (Box 15)
    - "Charley", 1967 (Box 15)
    - "Fan Song", undated (Box 15)
    - "The Farm", 1972 (Box 15)
    - "For Antonio Machado", 1967 (Box 15)
    - "For Minoru Nishida", undated (Box 15)
    - "From the Fastest Train", undated (Box 15)
    - "His Body Shrinks", 1971 (Box 15)
    - "Intersection", 1971 January-February (Box 15)
    - "Local Conditions", undated (Box 15)
    - "The Military", undated (Box 15)
    - "Peephole", undated (Box 15)
    - "Plaza at the Edo Palace", 1971 January-April (Box 15)
    - "Portrait of My Father Hunting Stones", 1967 August (Box 15)
    - "Prince Genji's Dance and Triumph", 1970 (Box 15)
    - "Process", 1971 March (Box 15)
    - "Reductive Reasoning of Telescopes", 1970 May (Box 15)
    - "Waiting for the Warden", 1970 (Box 15)
    - Printed matter and miscellaneous, 1969-1970, undated (Box 15)
    - Autograph letter from Lytton, Edward Bulwer-Lytton, undated (Box 15)
    - "Declension", 1972 (Box 15)
    - "An End of the Picaro", 1974, undated (Box 15)
    - "Keeping Distances", 1971-1973 (Box 15)
    - "For Mr Reed of Martha's Vineyard", 1971 January 2 (Box 15)
    - "The Military", undated (Box 15)
    - "Revolutions", 1973 December 25 (Box 15)
    - Roofs, 1971; 7 (Box 15)
    - "Winter Mountain Man", 1972 (Box 15)
    - "To Charley", undated (Box 15)
    - "Night Landing", undated (Box 15)
    - Thanksgiving Over the Water, 1992 March 24 (Box 15)
    - Drafts, worksheets, abandoned manuscripts, and others, undated (Box 15)
    - After the Hunt, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Man in the Open Air, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Seneca, A Cloak for Hercules; translated by Stephen Sandy, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Drafts and worksheets, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - Tack: Selected and New Poems, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Unsorted poems, undated (Box 16)
    - Man in the Open Air, 1988; 4 (Box 16)
    - "Justine," "Body," "Pledges," worksheets, undated (Box 16)
    - "Abandoned Houses," etc., worksheets, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - Thanksgiving Over the Water, 1991-1992 (Box 16)
    - Scales, 1998 (Box 16)
    - "Holy Life of St. Jerome" Cantata draft - Brant, Henry, undated (Box 16)
    - "Seeing Things: The Visionary Ardor of Seamus Heaney", 1993 (Box 16)
    - "Manifestations", 1999 (Box 16)
    - The Thread: New and Selected Poems, 1998, undated; 4 (Box 17)
    - "Second Thoughts", 1956-1957 (Box 17)
    - Black Box, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Aeschylus, "The Curse of the King"; translated by Stephen Sandy, 1997 (Box 17)
      Also titled "Seven Against Thebes."
    - Worksheets and drafts, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Thanksgiving Over the Water, undated (Box 17)
    - "A Low Profile" and "From Chinoiserie to Chinese Tombs and the Slag Hills: Notes on the Villanelle", 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - "Freestone", undated (Box 17)
    - "Seven Against Thebes" translated by Stephen Sandy, undated (Box 17)
    - "An Enlarging Pleasure" and "The One Day", undated (Box 17)
    - "More Than Anywhere", undated (Box 17)
    - Seven Against Thebes; translated by Stephen Sandy, 1997-1998; 2 (Box 17)
    - Poems, undated (Box 17)
    - Drafts and stories, 1990s (Box 17)
    - Black Box, 1998-2999, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Black Box, undated; 6 (Box 18)
    - Empty envelope, undated (Box 18)
    - Scales, undated (Box 18)
    - Poetry broadsides, 1969-1976 (Box 18)
    - Manifestations, 1997-1998 (Box 18)
    - Roofs, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Surface Impressions, 2001 November 9, undated; 2 (Box 18)
    - The Hawthorne Effect; "From Chinoiserie to Chinese Tombs and the Slag Hills: Notes on the Villanelle", 1980-1997 (Box 18)
    - "Keeping About: A Memory of Austin Warren" and "Salt of the Sky: James Merrill's Poetry", 1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Poems and Drafts - Balch Archive, 1962-1965, undated (Box 18)
    - Stresses in the Peaceable Kingdom, 1967 (Box 18)
    - "Hiroshima Pilot", 1970-1972 (Box 18)
    - "Banal Testament", 1970s (Box 18)
    - Poem drafts, undated (Box 18)
    - "Moving Screen", undated (Box 18)
    - "White Shore", 1970-1972 (Box 18)
    - "Shepherd", 1970-1971 (Box 18)
    - "Moving Out", 1995 (Box 18)
    - "Revolutions", circa 1970-1979 (Box 18)
    - Caroms, final proofs and original copy, 1960 (Box 18)
    - Wild Ducks, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Mary Baldwin, 1962; 2 (Box 18)
    - "New England Graveyard", undated (Box 18)
    - "Identity" - "And Night Folds In," "The Only Free Dragon is a Dead Dragon," "In Celebration, Out", 1958 (Box 18)
    - "Ice Cream is a Lenten Food", 1958 (Box 18)
    - "A War Folder", The Harvard Advocate, [1959] (Box 18)
    - "The Sultan Wears a Crimson Turban", undated (Box 18)
    - The Norway Spruce, 1964 (Box 18)
    - A. Fergus, "A Water Lily Painting Destroyed by Fire", 1964 October (Box 18)
    - "The Manchurian Candidate," Dunster Drama Review, 1962 November 16 (Box 18)
    - The Winthrop House, Lion Rampant, 1966 November (Box 18)
    - "New England Graveyard", 1961 September; 2 (Box 18)
    - "Seeing Things: The Visionary Ardor of Seamus Heaney", undated (Box 19)
    - "Easterly," Surface Impressions, 1999-2001 (Box 19)
    - Scales, 1991-2001 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous poem drafts, circa 1987-2002 (Box 19)
    - Weather Permitting, circa 2001 (Box 19)
    - Manuscripts and drafts, 1969, undated (Box 19)
    - Three Essays by Alan S., Jr., 1970s (Box 19)
    - "Vision and Speculation: Two Encounters with the American Landscape", undated (Box 19)
    - "Abandoned Houses," worksheets, undated (Box 19)
    - "Upcountry" and other drafts and worksheets, undated (Box 19)
    - "Wyoming", circa 1947 (Box 19)
    - The Yale Literary Magazine, 1954 October (Box 19)
      Other Finding Aids
      Includes "Overseas Highway" and "The Angels Prepare Persepolis for Time"
    - Drafts / Japan, undated (Box 19)
    - "Madagascar", undated (Box 19)
    - "Riding Thermals", Surface Impressions, worksheets, undated (Box 19)
    - "Antipodes," Surface Impressions, worksheets, undated (Box 19)
    - "Northway Tanka", 1973 August 15 (Box 19)
  - Other Papers
    Not arranged in any particular order.
    - Crossett Library Exhibits, 1993-1997 (Box 20)
    - Yale University Press, 1999-2001 (Box 20)
    - Bennington Tree Committee, 1995, undated (Box 20)
    - Vale Matters, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Navy, 1957-1989 (Box 20)
    - Javits/Department of Education, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
    - Fiscal - B.Y. - S.S., 1968-1970, undated (Box 20)
    - Offprints, proofs, Sandy, 1971, undated (Box 20)
    - Borestone Mt. Poetry Awards, 1962 May 15 (Box 20)
    - US Army / Discharge Notice, 1961 November 27 (Box 20)
    - New York Times, 1957 (Box 20)
    - Brown University Library, 1965 (Box 20)
    - Harvard Graduate Society, 1970 October 7 (Box 20)
    - Doodles, undated (Box 20)
    - Magazines, flyers, reviews - UICBY - Taconic, undated (Box 20)
    - Chautauqua, 1996, undated (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-2002, undated (Box 20)
    - Summer '87, 1984-1987 (Box 20)
    - Publication materials, undated (Box 20)
    - Sandy, Stephen, 1969-1977 (Box 20)
- February 2006 Acquisition, 1969; 5; 0.21; (1 box)
  The February 2006 Acquisition consists of material removed from books acquired from Stephen Sandy, including a letter to Barton L. St. Armand to Stephen Sandy, and a copy of a drawing of an unidentified man.
  - Copy of a drawing of an unidentified man, undated (Box 21)
  - Autograph letter signed from Barton L. St. Armand to Stephen Sandy, 1969 March 6 (Box 21)
- April 2006 Acquisition, 1992-1999; 6; 0.21; (1 box)
  The April 2006 Acquisition consists of material removed from books acquired from Stephen Sandy, including correspondence, writings, and clippings.
  - Autograph letter signed from "Sue" to Stephen Sandy, undated (Box 22)
    Removed from: Caldwell, Joseph, 1928-. Bread for the baker's child; a novel. Louisville: c2002.
  - Note from Julia Randall, undated (Box 22)
  - Biographical notes on Gerald Stern, typescript, with autograph manuscript corrections, undated (Box 22)
    Removed from: Stern, Gerald, 1925-. Paradise poems. New York: 1984.
  - Typed draft of introductory speech, undated (Box 22)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Note, newspaper clipping, and conference schedule, 1999, undated (Box 22)
- July 2006 Acquisition, circa 1970-2000; 7; (1 broadside folder)
  - Posters and broadside poem entitled "Post Card, Moss Garden", circa 1970-2000 (Box 23 (Broadside))
- August 2006 Acquisition, 1957-2006; 8; 4.21; (5 boxes)
  The July 2003 Acquisition consists of correspondence, writings, printed material, and other papers. The Correspondence and Subject Files consist chiefly of professional and personal letters from writers and literary organizations, documenting the literary community in which Sandy is active, and related papers. Other subject files consist of material relating to a particular person or topic (e.g. Ali Agha Shahid). Writings include drafts (autograph manuscript and typescript), proofs, and printed versions, some corrected. Other Papers include printed material and ephemera.
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - Academy of American Poets, 1993-2006, undated (Box 24)
    - Agha Shahid, Ali, 1999-2001 (Box 24)
    - Allen, William, 2002-2005, undated (Box 24)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Ammons, A. R., 1998-1999 (Box 24)
    - Armory, Rob, 2005-2006 (Box 24)
    - Ascher, Barbara, 2003-2006, undated (Box 24)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 2002-2005 (Box 24)
    - Bagley, Russ, circa 2004 (Box 24)
    - Belitt, Ben, 1984 November 14 (Box 24)
    - Bennington College, 1993-1999 (Box 24)
    - Bernold, André, 1997, undated (Box 24)
    - Blue Mountain Center, 2003-2006 (Box 24)
    - Boepple, Willard, 1984-2005 (Box 24)
    - Brock-Broido, Lucie, undated (Box 24)
    - Brookhouse, Christopher, 2003-2004 (Box 24)
    - Butt, Fowzy, 2005, undated (Box 24)
    - Caldwell, Joe, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
    - Campion, Peter, 2003-2004 (Box 24)
    - Carruth, Hayden, 2002-2005, undated (Box 24)
    - Chao, Phebe, 1997-2003 (Box 24)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1999-2002 (Box 24)
    - Chu, Ken, 2004 (Box 24)
    - Cohen, Brian, 2003, undated (Box 24)
    - Cooper, Wyn, 2004-2005, undated (Box 24)
    - Corbett, William and Coble, Gerald, 2004, undated (Box 24)
    - Correa, Raul, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1994-2005 (Box 24)
    - Cumming, Douglas O., 2003-2006, undated (Box 24)
    - Curtis, Susan, 1984-2006; 2 (Box 24)
    - Daniels, Kate, 2003 (Box 24)
    - Davison, Peter, 1986-2005 (Box 24)
    - Delanty, Greg, 2003-2004 (Box 24)
    - Delbanco, Nicholas, 1992-2005 (Box 24)
    - DeNiord, Chard, 1995-2004, undated (Box 24)
    - Dennis, Carl, 2002-2003, undated (Box 24)
    - Desai, Kiran, 1998 November 27 (Box 24)
    - Dove, Rita, 1989 April 24 (Box 24)
    - Ergene, Gökçen, 2001-2005 (Box 24)
    - Foster, Catherine, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Garrett, George, 1978-2005, undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - Grealy, Lucy, 2002, undated (Box 24)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
    - Gwira, Daniel, 2003-2005 (Box 24)
    - Hadas, Rachel, 1998-2006, undated (Box 24)
    - Hammer, Lanny, 2003 (Box 24)
    - Hoagland, Edward, 2002-2005 (Box 24)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, 2003 May 11 (Box 24)
    - Holland, Gil, 1994, undated (Box 24)